{"allRoundData":[{"name":"Round 0","timeLimitInSeconds":90,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswers":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"How old is Mike Harrison","answers":[{"answerText":"19","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"21","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"23","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"26","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Where does Mike Harrison live?","answers":[{"answerText":"Providence","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Worcester","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Scituate","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Cranston","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What time is Mike Harrison submitting this?","answers":[{"answerText":"7 PM","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"11 PM","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2 AM","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"How much effort in design did Mike Harrison put in this","answers":[{"answerText":"None","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"How many more questions does Mike Harrison have to put in this quiz before he is happy with it?","answers":[{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Is this a trick question?","answers":[{"answerText":"Yes","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"How many cups of coffee have I had tonight?","answers":[{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Here comes Peter Cotton Tail...","answers":[{"answerText":"Hopping down the bunny trail..","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Drinking tons of ginger ale..","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Just got back from bunny jail...","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Hopefully Mike doesn't fail..","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Banging your head against a wall burns ______ calories per hour","answers":[{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"150","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"300","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"600","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Grade on this Final Project","answers":[{"answerText":"An A","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"100","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Perfect","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"One Hundred","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Does adding questions from the website work? (This is a test..)","answers":[{"answerText":"Yes","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Did I seriously sort scores by alphabetical order instead of numerical order and have to fix it?","answers":[{"answerText":"Yes","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}